(Penny:)That was a really nice dinner.
(Penny:)- I'm glad you asked me out again.
- Me too. I missed you.
(Penny:)You see me all the time.
(Penny:)You sure you just don't miss the sex?
(Leonard:)Well, yeah, sex with you is pretty great.
Have you ever tried it? Heh, heh.
(Penny:)I have. You are not wrong.
(Penny:)If we're gonna try dating again,
we should take things slow.
(Leonard:)Oh, I can take it slow.
Did I tell you about my girIfriend
in high school, Karen Berberick?
(Leonard:)To this day she doesn't know
we were going out.
(Leonard:)Made it easier on her
when I broke things off.
(Penny:)Okay, well, maybe not that slow.
How about this:
(Leonard:)Are you familiar with the typical
development for computer software?
(Penny:)You know, just for fun,
Iet's say I'm not.
(Leonard:)Before an application is released,
they give it a trial run.
(Leonard:)We could do that.
(Leonard:)And if we hit a rough spot,
instead of getting mad, we say: